<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bocchi the Rock!</string>
    <string name="splash">by xsat93</string>
    <string name="myname">Satrio Mukti Prayoga</string>
    <string name="myemail">youremail123@domain.com</string>
    <string name="char_name">Character Name</string>
    <string name="description">Character Description</string>
    <string name="synop">Synopsis</string>
    <string name="age">Age : %1$s</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender : %1$s</string>
    <string name="synopsis">This application was created to introduce the characters in the anime Bocchi the Rock!\n\nSynopsis :\nYearning to make friends and perform live with a band, lonely and socially anxious Hitori "Bocchi" Gotou devotes her time to playing the guitar. On a fateful day, Bocchi meets the outgoing drummer Nijika Ijichi, who invites her to join Kessoku Band when their guitarist, Ikuyo Kita, flees before their first show. Soon after, Bocchi meets his final bandmate—the cool bassist Ryou Yamada.\n\nAlthough their first performance together was subpar, the girls felt empowered by their shared love for music, and they were soon rejoined by Kita. Finding happiness in performing, Bocchi and his bandmates put their hearts into improving as musicians while making the most of their fleeting high school days.\n\nThe source of information in this application comes from the website https://bocchi-the-rock.fandom.com/ and https://myanimelist.net/anime/47917/Bocchi_the_Rock \n\nThis application was created to complete final submission of \"Learning Path 2 Android Developer\" at www.dicoding.com, entitled \"Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula\".</string>
    <string name="desc_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="desc_about">About Button</string>
    <string name="desc_icon">Icon Toolbar</string>
    <string name="desc_logo_splash">Logo Splash</string>
    <string name="desc_photo">Photo</string>
    <string name="desc_share">Share Button</string>
    <color name="action_bar_color">#FF69B4</color>
    <color name="bgmain">#FF99CC</color>
    <color name="txtsplash">#37474F</color>

    <drawable name="mysplash">@drawable/splash</drawable>
    <drawable name="myphoto">@drawable/profil</drawable>
    <drawable name="icon_back">@drawable/ico_back</drawable>
    <drawable name="icon_share">@drawable/ico_share</drawable>
    <drawable name="ico_toolbar">@drawable/icon_toolbar</drawable>
    <drawable name="ico_profile">@drawable/ico_profil</drawable>

    <string-array name="char_name">
        <item>Hitori Gotoh</item>
        <item>Ikuyo Kita</item>
        <item>Nijika Ijichi</item>
        <item>Ryo Yamada</item>
        <item>Seika Ijichi</item>
        <item>Kikuri Hiroi</item>
        <item>Shima Iwashita</item>
        <item>Eliza Shimizu</item>
        <item>PA-san</item>
        <item>Ginjiro Yoshida</item>
        <item>Futari Gotoh</item>
        <item>Michiyo Gotoh</item>
        <item>Naoki Gotoh</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_gender">
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Male</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_age">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>29</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>21</item>
        <item>24</item>
        <item>37</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>Unknown</item>
        <item>Unknown</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>Hitori Gotoh, often referred by her bandmates as Bocchi-chan, is the titular main protagonist of the manga and anime series, Bocchi the Rock!. She is in the first year of Shuka High School and is in charge of the guitar and lyrics of the band, Kessoku Band. \n\nAn extremely timid and introverted first-year student in high school. She is in charge of the responsibility of playing the lead guitar for Kessoku Band. She aspires to perform in a band that could showcase even a reserved girl\'s talent, hence she began playing the guitar. Although her skill is the real deal, she struggles to exhibit it proficiently in a band or in front of an audience. Additionally, she possesses a habit of saying "Ah" before she speaks. \n\nHitori struggles with interpersonal relationships and often shies away from first encounters. She is frequently seen wearing a jersey and spends most of her time at home playing the guitar in a dark closet, hardly ever venturing out. Whenever a situation arises, she tries to hide in a trash can, cardboard box, or other objects, even performing her first live house show from inside a cardboard box. Despite her attempts to liven things up, she usually fails, either by slipping up or overdoing it. She craves approval from others, likely as a reaction to her personality. She is also, however, aware that she tends to scrutinize others and often feels pressured and anxious.</item>
        <item>Ikuyo Kita is one of the main characters in the manga and anime series, Bocchi the Rock!. She is in the first year of Shuka High School and is in charge of the guitar and vocals of the band, Kessoku Band. She has great admiration for Ryo Yamada, after seeing her street concert. \n\nA bright and popular first year of high school. She is in charge of the guitar and vocals of Kessoku Band. She is a cheerful character who likes to interact with people and can talk to her with a smile without hesitation, even when she meets her for the first time. She looks up to Ryo, and her feelings can go too far. She often takes photos and uploads to Isosta. \n\nKita has red hair with grown-out bangs and yellow eyes. In her uniform, she wears a white chocolate sailor uniform with long sleeves, six yellow buttons at the side and red ribbon ties, a short gray pleated skirt, white socks, and maroon shoes.</item>
        <item>Nijika Ijichi is one of the main characters in the manga and anime series, Bocchi the Rock!. She is a second-year student of Shimokitazawa High School and is the drummer in the band, Kessoku Band. \n\nAn energetic and cheerful second-year high school student. She is the drummer of Kessoku Band. The organizer of her band who takes care of Hitori was already joined Kessoku Band. She has an older sister, Seika, who is the manager of the live house "STARRY" and has a special feeling for the live house. \n\nNijika has long blonde hair with a floating triangle-like ahoge worn in a side ponytail and vermilion eyes. In her uniform, she wears a white long-sleeve uniform with a tucked skirt and red ribbon with big polka dots, a dark blue pleated skirt, white socks, and red sneakers with white laces.</item>
        <item>Ryo Yamada is one of the main characters in the manga and anime series, Bocchi the Rock!. She is in her second year at Shimokitazawa High School and is the bassist of the band, Kessoku Band. She works a part-time job at the live house STARRY with Nijika Ijichi. \n\nA cool and solitary second-year high school student. She is the bassist of Kessoku Band and Nijika\'s best friend. Her hobbies are out of the ordinary, and she rejoices when called a weirdo. She lives with a wealthy family but never has any money because she spends it all on instruments. She occasionally eats weeds to get rid of her hunger. \n\nRyo has short blue hair with two black square hair clips on the right side of her bangs and yellow eyes, with a mole on her left cheek. Ryo\'s uniform consists of a collared white shirt worn with a black ribbon, a dark blue pleated skirt, black leggings, maroon or brown loafers, and a matching long sleeved sweater. This outfit is similar to most Japanese high school uniforms (seifuku).</item>
        <item>Seika Ijichi is the manager of the live house, STARRY. She is the older sister of Nijika Ijichi. \n\nSeika has long blonde hair with floating triangle-like ahoge and orange eyes. She is commonly wearing a black wide-neck shirt revealing red shoulder straps, as well as a tight black choker around her neck. \n\nSeika used to be a bandsman - a guitarist herself, and her ability was such that the label talked about scouts. She sometimes hits Nijika and the members of Kessoku Band in her mouth,[11] but in reality, she thinks of Kessoku Band more than anyone else. Although she didn\'t know that Bocchi was "guitarhero", she was quick to realize her talent as a guitarist. She can be quite of a tsundere at times, especially when it comes to her little sister Nijika. For example, Nijika claimed that Seika opened Starry for her, even though Seika will never admit that. Also, it was known that she always saved a spot, wanting Kessoku Band to play even though she pretended she did not want them to. She also sleeps with her soft toys despite her age.</item>
        <item>Kikuri Hiroi is a supporting character of the manga and anime series, Bocchi the Rock!, and the protagonist of the spinoff manga Bocchi the Rock! Gaiden: Hiroi Kikuri no Fukazake Nikki. She is the bassist and the vocalist of the band, SICK HACK. \n\nKikuri has long dark pink hair worn in a side braid tied with a dark brown ribbon and magenta-purple eyes. In the manga, she wears a hanafuda card earring depicting a lotus in both ears. She wears a simple green dress with a black and white jacket over it and a pair of geta. In the manga, the lower half of her dress has numerous lycoris radiata/spider lily flower patterns. She also wears black nail polish on both her fingernails and toenails and is often shown with sharp teeth. In the manga, she has a tribal circle-looking tattoo on the back of her right hand. \n\nOnce when she was drunk in front of the station, she happened to meet Bocchi who was trying to sell tickets. Despite Bocchi\'s initial resistance due to her altered state, they eventually bonded and Kikuri made her perform an improvised session live on the spot where she noticed Bocchi\'s talents. It was then that a more empathic and mature side of her was first shown. At that time, after visiting the performance of Kessoku Band with a ticket purchased from Bocchi, she frequently appeared in STARRY. However, she still proves herself to be an annoying guest due to her frequent drunkenness.</item>
        <item>Shima Iwashita is a supporting character from Bocchi the Rock!. She is in charge of drums of the band, SICK HACK. \n\nShe has short dark hair and red eyes, and wears manly clothes such as long pants and a typical men\'s PE jacket. At first glance, she would be mistaken as a man due to her fashion and hairstyle. \n\nWhile seems boyish, Shima is actually a polite person as she tried to apologise to Kessoku Band for Kikuri\'s misdeeds towards them in addition to greeting them politely and sincerely, as well to others she meet. The only exception to her nice treatment is to Kikuri herself, where she always reprimands her due to her alcoholic and sloppy lifestyle. However when it comes to performance, she doesn\'t hold back on her skills, and as commented by Bocchi, "her irregular beats will make anyone lose their minds". In high school, Shima was described as "very helpful" and was a favourite among the students.</item>
        <item>Eliza Shimizu is a supporting character from Bocchi the Rock!. She is in charge of guitar of the band, SICK HACK. She originally came from England, and moved to Japan 3 years ago so she could attend Comiket and be in an Ani-song cover band. She also made some doujinshi on top of her band activities. \n\nEliza has bright yellow long hair with denim blue eyes, and first appears wearing a yukata with its top loosened, revealing her innerwear. \n\nShe introduces herself as a cheerful person, which already shows along with her friendly side when meeting with Kessoku Band for the first time in Shinjuku FOLT before their live. She also not hesitated to claim she is a weeb/anime otaku, admitting her reason to come to Japan was merely to be able to attend Comiket and be in an Ani-song cover band. Her otaku behaviour is pretty strong that she possesses a lot of anime knowledge and all its trope, and always passionate when it comes to such conversation. She also tend to spend all of her money in Comima (in-universe version of Comic Market/Comiket). She also has various anime merchandises like the keychain set of Slow Loop characters attached to her phone case. When it comes to drawing doujinshi, she is pretty strict with her deadline that even band activities cannot bother her.</item>
        <item>PA-san is an unnamed public address sound engineer of STARRY. She dropped out of high school because she could never wake up early and failed too many classes. It is also the reason why she has her current night job. She works privately as a virtual YouTuber under the name Alto Otogi publishing gameplay videos. \n\nPA-san is a pale-skinned young woman with long black hair and green eyes. She is dressed in a goth style, with a black choker, a gray dress with a long black coat over it, and piercings. \n\nDespite her somewhat creepy appearance which first scares Bocchi, PA-san is very kind, easygoing, and friendly.</item>
        <item>Ginjiro Yoshida is a supporting character from Bocchi the Rock!. He is the manager of FOLT, a live house in Shinjuku where SICK HACK always makes performances there. His favorite genre is punk rock. \n\nYoshida is middle aged man with black hair and green eyes, he also have noticeable bags under his eyes. \n\nWhile at a glance seems like a rough person and hard to be approached, he is actually soft and friendly, sometimes can be considered feminine when he speaks. However, he can be stern to anybody that troubled him, especially Hiroi who owes him a lot of money due to her mishaps in the live house.</item>
        <item>Futari Gotoh is a supporting character of Bocchi the Rock! manga and anime series. She is the little sister of Hitori, who meets everyone without getting afraid. \n\nFutari has neck-length pink hair with a lock of hair on both sides and dark aqua eyes. She wears a sailor uniform with no skirt, a star, and a dark blue ribbon and white lines. \n\nFutari is not afraid to meet new people for the first time. She often inflicts mental damage (especially on Hitori) by innocently saying things that gouge the opponent\'s heart.</item>
        <item>Michiyo Gotoh is the mother of Hitori Gotoh and Futari Gotoh as well as wife to Naoki Gotoh. \n\nHitori\'s mother is always there to listen to her daughter and offer her advice. She is also a great cook, and she loves to make Hitori her favorite meals. \n\nIn one episode, Hitori\'s mother helps her to join the rock band, Go! Go! Rock! Hitori is initially hesitant to join the band, but her mother encourages her to try it out. With her mother\'s support, Hitori eventually overcomes her fear of public speaking and becomes a valuable member of the band.</item>
        <item>Naoki Gotoh is the father of both Hitori Gotoh and Futari Gotoh as well as the husband of Michiyo. Originally was the owner of Hitori\'s first guitar before passing it to her, and was in a band during his youth. \n\nNaoki is a kind and supportive father who is always there for his daughters. He is also a talented musician, and he is the one who gave Hitori her first guitar. \n\nIn the first episode of the anime, Hitori breaks her guitar during a performance at the school festival. She is devastated and apologizes to her father, but he tells her not to worry about it. He also suggests that she buy a new guitar, and he helps her find one that is perfect for her..</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/hitori</item>
        <item>@drawable/ikuyo</item>
        <item>@drawable/nijika</item>
        <item>@drawable/yamada</item>
        <item>@drawable/seika</item>
        <item>@drawable/kikuri</item>
        <item>@drawable/shima</item>
        <item>@drawable/eliza</item>
        <item>@drawable/pasan</item>
        <item>@drawable/ginjirou</item>
        <item>@drawable/futari</item>
        <item>@drawable/michiyo</item>
        <item>@drawable/naoki</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>